Life Assurance Kenya have formalized a
bank assurance partnership to offer
insurance products particularly for
affluent client. The collaboration
introduces life uh life a high value
protection product with coverage of up
to 500 million shillings designated for
individuals seeking advanced wealth and
legacy planning solutions. A six-month
pilot program for live life generated
over 2.6 6 billion shillings in some
assured indicating market receptability.
According to the financial firm, these
initiative aligns with the growth of
Kenya's affluent demographic and the
expanding uh bank assurance sector.